###### Privacy Policy

May 2022
--------

At customcountdown.io, I understand the importance of your data and take all necessary measures to ensure its security. Any information you provide through a form, such as clock and support data, IP address, username with hashed password, and email (if voluntarily provided), is collected for the sole purpose of improving our services. Please note that as the administrator of customcountdown.io, I have full access to all information associated with your clock, including its name, ID, and URL. However, to protect your privacy, I will remove the clock, its associated short URL, and ALL other data from our records five days after the clock's expiry. It is worth noting that some third party services and APIs used by customcountdown.io may have their own privacy policies. I use a self-hosted, in-house analytics system that respects the Do Not Track (DNT) policy. You can enable DNT if you wish. As the owner of customcountdown.io, I want to assure you that I will never sell your data to any third party.

* * *

* * *

[ToS](https://customcountdown.io/tos.txt) - [Refunds](https://customcountdown.io/refunds.txt)  
_Customcountdown.io is a privately owned website, and it is not affiliated with any company or organization._

Legal
-----

Updated at 2023-01-20

Custom Countdown (“we,” “our,” or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by Custom Countdown.

This Privacy Policy applies to our website, and its associated subdomains (collectively, our “Service”) alongside our application, Custom Countdown. By accessing or using our Service, you signify that you have read, understood, and agree to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. This Privacy Policy was created with [Termify](https://termify.io/).

Definitions and key terms
=========================

To help explain things as clearly as possible in this Privacy Policy, every time any of these terms are referenced, are strictly defined as:

* Cookie: small amount of data generated by a website and saved by your web browser. It is used to identify your browser, provide analytics, remember information about you such as your language preference or login information.
* Company: when this policy mentions “Company,” “we,” “us,” or “our,” it refers to Custom Countdown, that is responsible for your information under this Privacy Policy.
* Country: where Custom Countdown or the owners/founders of Custom Countdown are based, in this case is The United States of America
* Customer: refers to the company, organization or person that signs up to use the Custom Countdown Service to manage the relationships with your consumers or service users.
* Device: any internet connected device such as a phone, tablet, computer or any other device that can be used to visit Custom Countdown and use the services.
* IP address: Every device connected to the Internet is assigned a number known as an Internet protocol (IP) address. These numbers are usually assigned in geographic blocks. An IP address can often be used to identify the location from which a device is connecting to the Internet.
* Personnel: refers to those individuals who are employed by Custom Countdown or are under contract to perform a service on behalf of one of the parties.
* Personal Data: any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.
* Service: refers to the service provided by Custom Countdown as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this platform.
* Third-party service: refers to advertisers, contest sponsors, promotional and marketing partners, and others who provide our content or whose products or services we think may interest you.
* Website: Custom Countdown's site, which can be accessed via this URL: https://customcountdown.io
* You: a person or entity that is registered with Custom Countdown to use the Services.

What Information Do We Collect?
===============================

We collect information from you when you visit our website, register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

* Name / Username
* Email Addresses
* Password

How Do We Use The Information We Collect?
=========================================

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
* To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
* To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
* To process transactions
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
* To send periodic emails

When does Custom Countdown use end user information from third parties?
=======================================================================

Custom Countdown will collect End User Data necessary to provide the Custom Countdown services to our customers.

End users may voluntarily provide us with information they have made available on social media websites. If you provide us with any such information, we may collect publicly available information from the social media websites you have indicated. You can control how much of your information social media websites make public by visiting these websites and changing your privacy settings.

When does Custom Countdown use customer information from third parties?
=======================================================================

We receive some information from the third parties when you contact us. For example, when you submit your email address to us to show interest in becoming a Custom Countdown customer, we receive information from a third party that provides automated fraud detection services to Custom Countdown. We also occasionally collect information that is made publicly available on social media websites. You can control how much of your information social media websites make public by visiting these websites and changing your privacy settings.

Do we share the information we collect with third parties?
==========================================================

We may share the information that we collect, both personal and non-personal, with third parties such as advertisers, contest sponsors, promotional and marketing partners, and others who provide our content or whose products or services we think may interest you. We may also share it with our current and future affiliated companies and business partners, and if we are involved in a merger, asset sale or other business reorganization, we may also share or transfer your personal and non-personal information to our successors-in-interest.

We may engage trusted third party service providers to perform functions and provide services to us, such as hosting and maintaining our servers and the website, database storage and management, e-mail management, storage marketing, credit card processing, customer service and fulfilling orders for products and services you may purchase through the website. We will likely share your personal information, and possibly some non-personal information, with these third parties to enable them to perform these services for us and for you.

We may share portions of our log file data, including IP addresses, for analytics purposes with third parties such as web analytics partners, application developers, and ad networks. If your IP address is shared, it may be used to estimate general location and other technographics such as connection speed, whether you have visited the website in a shared location, and type of the device used to visit the website. They may aggregate information about our advertising and what you see on the website and then provide auditing, research and reporting for us and our advertisers.   We may also disclose personal and non-personal information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in order to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect our rights and interests or those of a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to otherwise comply with applicable court orders, laws, rules and regulations.

Where and when is information collected from customers and end users?
=====================================================================

Custom Countdown will collect personal information that you submit to us. We may also receive personal information about you from third parties as described above.

How Do We Use Your Email Address?
=================================

By submitting your email address on this website, you agree to receive emails from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking on the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do. By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow us to use your email address for customer audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific people who have opted-in to receive communications from us. Email addresses submitted only through the order processing page will be used for the sole purpose of sending you information and updates pertaining to your order. If, however, you have provided the same email to us through another method, we may use it for any of the purposes stated in this Policy. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How Long Do We Keep Your Information?
=====================================

We keep your information only so long as we need it to provide Custom Countdown to you and fulfill the purposes described in this policy. This is also the case for anyone that we share your information with and who carries out services on our behalf. When we no longer need to use your information and there is no need for us to keep it to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, we’ll either remove it from our systems or depersonalize it so that we can't identify you.

How Do We Protect Your Information?
===================================

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) is never kept on file. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the absolute security of any information you transmit to Custom Countdown or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

Could my information be transferred to other countries?
=======================================================

Custom Countdown is incorporated in The United States of America. Information collected via our website, through direct interactions with you, or from use of our help services may be transferred from time to time to our offices or personnel, or to third parties, located throughout the world, and may be viewed and hosted anywhere in the world, including countries that may not have laws of general applicability regulating the use and transfer of such data. To the fullest extent allowed by applicable law, by using any of the above, you voluntarily consent to the trans-border transfer and hosting of such information.

Is the information collected through the Custom Countdown Service secure?
=========================================================================

We take precautions to protect the security of your information. We have physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard, prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use your information. However, neither people nor security systems are foolproof, including encryption systems. In addition, people can commit intentional crimes, make mistakes or fail to follow policies. Therefore, while we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If applicable law imposes any non-disclaimable duty to protect your personal information, you agree that intentional misconduct will be the standards used to measure our compliance with that duty.

Can I update or correct my information?
=======================================

The rights you have to request updates or corrections to the information Custom Countdown collects depend on your relationship with Custom Countdown. Personnel may update or correct their information as detailed in our internal company employment policies.

Customers have the right to request the restriction of certain uses and disclosures of personally identifiable information as follows. You can contact us in order to (1) update or correct your personally identifiable information, (2) change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you receive from us, or (3) delete the personally identifiable information maintained about you on our systems (subject to the following paragraph), by cancelling your account. Such updates, corrections, changes and deletions will have no effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such update, correction, change or deletion. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our system. The need to back up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. Promptly after receiving your request, all personal information stored in databases we actively use, and other readily searchable media will be updated, corrected, changed or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as and to the extent reasonably and technically practicable.

If you are an end user and wish to update, delete, or receive any information we have about you, you may do so by contacting the organization of which you are a customer.

Sale of Business
================

We reserve the right to transfer information to a third party in the event of a sale, merger or other transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of Custom Countdown or any of its Corporate Affiliates (as defined herein), or that portion of Custom Countdown or any of its Corporate Affiliates to which the Service relates, or in the event that we discontinue our business or file a petition or have filed against us a petition in bankruptcy, reorganization or similar proceeding, provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Affiliates
==========

We may disclose information (including personal information) about you to our Corporate Affiliates. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Corporate Affiliate" means any person or entity which directly or indirectly controls, is controlled by or is under common control with Custom Countdown, whether by ownership or otherwise. Any information relating to you that we provide to our Corporate Affiliates will be treated by those Corporate Affiliates in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Governing Law
=============

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of The United States of America without regard to its conflict of laws provision. You consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in connection with any action or dispute arising between the parties under or in connection with this Privacy Policy except for those individuals who may have rights to make claims under Privacy Shield, or the Swiss-US framework.

The laws of The United States of America, excluding its conflicts of law rules, shall govern this Agreement and your use of the website. Your use of the website may also be subject to other local, state, national, or international laws.

By using Custom Countdown or contacting us directly, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you should not engage with our website, or use our services. Continued use of the website, direct engagement with us, or following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy that do not significantly affect the use or disclosure of your personal information will mean that you accept those changes.

Your Consent
============

We've updated our Privacy Policy to provide you with complete transparency into what is being set when you visit our site and how it's being used. By using our website, registering an account, or making a purchase, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

Links to Other Websites
=======================

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by Custom Countdown. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy or opinions expressed in such websites, and such websites are not investigated, monitored or checked for accuracy or completeness by us. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Services to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our platform, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Such third parties may use their own cookies or other methods to collect information about you.

Advertising
===========

This website may contain third party advertisements and links to third party sites. Custom Countdown does not make any representation as to the accuracy or suitability of any of the information contained in those advertisements or sites and does not accept any responsibility or liability for the conduct or content of those advertisements and sites and the offerings made by the third parties.

Advertising keeps Custom Countdown and many of the websites and services you use free of charge. We work hard to make sure that ads are safe, unobtrusive, and as relevant as possible.

Third party advertisements and links to other sites where goods or services are advertised are not endorsements or recommendations by Custom Countdown of the third party sites, goods or services. Custom Countdown takes no responsibility for the content of any of the ads, promises made, or the quality/reliability of the products or services offered in all advertisements.

Cookies for Advertising
=======================

These cookies collect information over time about your online activity on the website and other online services to make online advertisements more relevant and effective to you. This is known as interest-based advertising. They also perform functions like preventing the same ad from continuously reappearing and ensuring that ads are properly displayed for advertisers. Without cookies, it’s really hard for an advertiser to reach its audience, or to know how many ads were shown and how many clicks they received.

Cookies
=======

Custom Countdown uses "Cookies" to identify the areas of our website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to enhance the performance and functionality of our website but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality like videos may become unavailable or you would be required to enter your login details every time you visit the website as we would not be able to remember that you had logged in previously. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.

Blocking and disabling cookies and similar technologies
=======================================================

Wherever you're located you may also set your browser to block cookies and similar technologies, but this action may block our essential cookies and prevent our website from functioning properly, and you may not be able to fully utilize all of its features and services. You should also be aware that you may also lose some saved information (e.g. saved login details, site preferences) if you block cookies on your browser. Different browsers make different controls available to you. Disabling a cookie or category of cookie does not delete the cookie from your browser, you will need to do this yourself from within your browser, you should visit your browser's help menu for more information.

Kids' Privacy
=============

We do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us. If We become aware that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from Our servers.

Changes To Our Privacy Policy
=============================

We may change our Service and policies, and we may need to make changes to this Privacy Policy so that they accurately reflect our Service and policies. Unless otherwise required by law, we will notify you (for example, through our Service) before we make changes to this Privacy Policy and give you an opportunity to review them before they go into effect. Then, if you continue to use the Service, you will be bound by the updated Privacy Policy. If you do not want to agree to this or any updated Privacy Policy, you can delete your account.

Third-Party Services
====================

We may display, include or make available third-party content (including data, information, applications and other products services) or provide links to third-party websites or services ("Third- Party Services").

You acknowledge and agree that Custom Countdown shall not be responsible for any Third-Party Services, including their accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality or any other aspect thereof. Custom Countdown does not assume and shall not have any liability or responsibility to you or any other person or entity for any Third-Party Services.

Third-Party Services and links thereto are provided solely as a convenience to you and you access and use them entirely at your own risk and subject to such third parties' terms and conditions.

Tracking Technologies
=====================

* Local Storage  

    Local Storage sometimes known as DOM storage, provides web apps with methods and protocols for storing client-side data. Web storage supports persistent data storage, similar to cookies but with a greatly enhanced capacity and no information stored in the HTTP request header.

* Sessions  

    $elnombre uses "Sessions" to identify the areas of our website that you have visited. A Session is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser.

Information about General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
===========================================================

We may be collecting and using information from you if you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), and in this section of our Privacy Policy we are going to explain exactly how and why is this data collected, and how we maintain this data under protection from being replicated or used in the wrong way.

What is GDPR?
=============

GDPR is an EU-wide privacy and data protection law that regulates how EU residents' data is protected by companies and enhances the control the EU residents have, over their personal data.

The GDPR is relevant to any globally operating company and not just the EU-based businesses and EU residents. Our customers’ data is important irrespective of where they are located, which is why we have implemented GDPR controls as our baseline standard for all our operations worldwide.

What is personal data?
======================

Any data that relates to an identifiable or identified individual. GDPR covers a broad spectrum of information that could be used on its own, or in combination with other pieces of information, to identify a person. Personal data extends beyond a person’s name or email address. Some examples include financial information, political opinions, genetic data, biometric data, IP addresses, physical address, sexual orientation, and ethnicity.

The Data Protection Principles include requirements such as:

* Personal data collected must be processed in a fair, legal, and transparent way and should only be used in a way that a person would reasonably expect.
* Personal data should only be collected to fulfil a specific purpose and it should only be used for that purpose. Organizations must specify why they need the personal data when they collect it.
* Personal data should be held no longer than necessary to fulfil its purpose.
* People covered by the GDPR have the right to access their own personal data. They can also request a copy of their data, and that their data be updated, deleted, restricted, or moved to another organization.

Why is GDPR important?
======================

GDPR adds some new requirements regarding how companies should protect individuals' personal data that they collect and process. It also raises the stakes for compliance by increasing enforcement and imposing greater fines for breach. Beyond these facts it's simply the right thing to do. At Custom Countdown we strongly believe that your data privacy is very important and we already have solid security and privacy practices in place that go beyond the requirements of this new regulation.

Individual Data Subject's Rights - Data Access, Portability and Deletion
========================================================================

We are committed to helping our customers meet the data subject rights requirements of GDPR. Custom Countdown processes or stores all personal data in fully vetted, DPA compliant vendors. We do store all conversation and personal data for up to 6 years unless your account is deleted. In which case, we dispose of all data in accordance with our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, but we will not hold it longer than 60 days.

We are aware that if you are working with EU customers, you need to be able to provide them with the ability to access, update, retrieve and remove personal data. We got you! We've been set up as self service from the start and have always given you access to your data and your customers data. Our customer support team is here for you to answer any questions you might have about working with the API.

California Residents
====================

The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) requires us to disclose categories of Personal Information we collect and how we use it, the categories of sources from whom we collect Personal Information, and the third parties with whom we share it, which we have explained above.

We are also required to communicate information about rights California residents have under California law. You may exercise the following rights:

* Right to Know and Access. You may submit a verifiable request for information regarding the: (1) categories of Personal Information we collect, use, or share; (2) purposes for which categories of Personal Information are collected or used by us; (3) categories of sources from which we collect Personal Information; and (4) specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.
* Right to Equal Service. We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.
* Right to Delete. You may submit a verifiable request to close your account and we will delete Personal Information about you that we have collected.
* Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

We do not sell the Personal Information of our users.

For more information about these rights, please contact us.

California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)
==================================================

CalOPPA requires us to disclose categories of Personal Information we collect and how we use it, the categories of sources from whom we collect Personal Information, and the third parties with whom we share it, which we have explained above.

CalOPPA users have the following rights:

* Right to Know and Access. You may submit a verifiable request for information regarding the: (1) categories of Personal Information we collect, use, or share; (2) purposes for which categories of Personal Information are collected or used by us; (3) categories of sources from which we collect Personal Information; and (4) specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.
* Right to Equal Service. We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.
* Right to Delete. You may submit a verifiable request to close your account and we will delete Personal Information about you that we have collected.
* Right to request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

We do not sell the Personal Information of our users.

For more information about these rights, please contact us.

Contact Us
==========

Don't hesitate to contact us if you have any questions.

* Via this Link: [https://customcountdown.io/email-con](https://customcountdown.io/email-con)

Close

##### Captcha help

Reset Captcha [Login and skip](https://customcountdown.io/user)

* * *

Custom Countdown use [Turnstile](https://www.cloudflare.com/products/turnstile/) as a CAPTCHA.

_More filtering, coming soon_

###### ! Default  

Posted on: **launch/ unknown**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### \*Bonus\* ~ Earth  

Posted on: **launch/ unknown**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### \*Bonus\* ~ HD Dark Bule Abstract  

Posted on: **launch/ unknown**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### \*Bonus\* ~ Thunderstorm Wallpaper Clouds  

Posted on: **launch/ unknown**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### 4-Dimensional space into 3D  

Posted on: **June 14, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### 80s Retro Landscape  

Posted on: **September 28, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Abstract 3D Polygonal  

Posted on: **February 22, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Abstract Cosmic Background  

Posted on: **August 24, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Abstract Pink/Blue Neon  

Posted on: **November 09, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Acrylic Colors in Water  

Posted on: **July 06, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Acrylic Colors in Water (2)  

Posted on: **July 06, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Ascending Glowing Lines  

Posted on: **May 10, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Astronaut Space Walk  

Posted on: **February 01, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Astronaut in Space  

Posted on: **August 09, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Beach  

Posted on: **December 28, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Big Data Network  

Posted on: **January 11, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Black Hole Over Star Field  

Posted on: **October 19, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Blaues Meer  

Posted on: **December 07, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Blockchain (concept)  

Posted on: **May 10, 2023**  
Unconfirmed AI Image

Select Report tagging error

###### Brick Wall With Neon Lights  

Posted on: **November 23, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Cafe Table  

Posted on: **April 26, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Celebration  

Posted on: **June 07, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Chess Piece on Chessboard  

Posted on: **March 29, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### City at Night  

Posted on: **April 05, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Cityscape With Neon Light  

Posted on: **November 09, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Cloud Illuminated With Neon Light  

Posted on: **August 31, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Colored Dynamic Spots  

Posted on: **December 21, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Contemporary Architecture  

Posted on: **February 08, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Cosmic Galaxy  

Posted on: **October 19, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Cosmic Portal  

Posted on: **March 22, 2023**  
Unconfirmed AI Image

Select Report tagging error

###### Crystal Rocks  

Posted on: **September 21, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Digital Illustration of Light Bulb (UHD)  

Posted on: **March 15, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Egyptian Pyramids in Future Desert  

Posted on: **June 21, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Empty Modern Office  

Posted on: **February 08, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Empty Night Nature  

Posted on: **May 17, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Explosion of Colors  

Posted on: **June 29, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Expressway  

Posted on: **August 03, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Fluorescent Square  

Posted on: **May 10, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Full Moon on Sea at Night  

Posted on: **January 04, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Futuristic City  

Posted on: **July 12, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Futuristic City  

Posted on: **July 13, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Futuristic Connect Circles  

Posted on: **January 11, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Geometric Shapes  

Posted on: **December 21, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Global Network Connection  

Posted on: **August 16, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Glowing Geometric Triangle  

Posted on: **August 17, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Glowing Laser Ring  

Posted on: **August 24, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Glowing Lightning Symbol  

Posted on: **August 17, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Glowing Neon Rectangular  

Posted on: **April 19, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Glowing Panels  

Posted on: **September 21, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Glowing Ring  

Posted on: **April 19, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Glowing Ring, Rocks Flying  

Posted on: **November 16, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Glowing Stormy Cloud  

Posted on: **September 07, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Graduation  

Posted on: **May 31, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Great Wall  

Posted on: **October 26, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Great Wave in Ocean  

Posted on: **October 05, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Green Forest  

Posted on: **July 20, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Guitars and Drums (UHD)  

Posted on: **March 15, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Hands of Robot and Human Touching  

Posted on: **July 26, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Hexagonal Abstract  

Posted on: **launch/ unknown**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Highway Through Smart City  

Posted on: **April 12, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Hurricane  

Posted on: **December 28, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Interior of Futuristic Laboratory  

Posted on: **July 05, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Lake Landscape Starry Night  

Posted on: **January 04, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Laser Show  

Posted on: **November 30, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Light Trails at Night  

Posted on: **January 18, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Liquid Abstract Background  

Posted on: **December 14, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Liquid Colors  

Posted on: **November 02, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Luminous Cuboid  

Posted on: **July 19, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Luxury Camping  

Posted on: **April 26, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Luxury Penthouse Bedroom at Night  

Posted on: **January 25, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Magical Book  

Posted on: **March 29, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Minimalist Fishing Boats  

Posted on: **July 26, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Minimalist Fishing Boats (2)  

Posted on: **August 02, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Minimalist Landscape  

Posted on: **August 02, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Modern Abstract Background  

Posted on: **February 22, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Modern Beach Home  

Posted on: **May 25, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Modern Interior Design  

Posted on: **June 28, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Modern Living Room  

Posted on: **March 01, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Modern Living Room With Fireplace  

Posted on: **March 01, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Modern Luxury Patio  

Posted on: **August 09, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Mountain Green Field  

Posted on: **February 15, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Mountains and Hills Painting  

Posted on: **October 26, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Mystical Cloud and Cross Sign Glowing  

Posted on: **September 07, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Mystical Forest  

Posted on: **September 28, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Natural Forest Sunrise  

Posted on: **July 27, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Nature With Wooden Houses  

Posted on: **February 15, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Nebula Galaxy  

Posted on: **January 25, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Neon Cat  

Posted on: **April 12, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Neon Cube  

Posted on: **November 02, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Neon Geometric Shape  

Posted on: **August 31, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Neon Palm Tree  

Posted on: **May 17, 2023**  
Unconfirmed AI Image

Select Report tagging error

###### Night Landscape  

Posted on: **July 27, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Night Landscape  

Posted on: **November 23, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Northern Lights  

Posted on: **November 16, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Ocean Blue Marbling  

Posted on: **June 22, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Papagayo Strand  

Posted on: **December 07, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Pink Blue Neon Light Square  

Posted on: **June 29, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Pink Blue Neon Lights  

Posted on: **June 15, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Pyramid and Steps Neon  

Posted on: **June 22, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Red and Blue Neon  

Posted on: **September 14, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Red and Blue Neon Corridor  

Posted on: **September 14, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Retro Interior of a Spaceship  

Posted on: **October 12, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Rock Climbing Landscape  

Posted on: **July 19, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Sci-Fi Fire With Hypnotic Waves  

Posted on: **March 08, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Sci-Fi Futuristic Space Station  

Posted on: **June 21, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Sci-Fi Hallway  

Posted on: **June 28, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Silhouette Standing on the Edge of a Skyscraper  

Posted on: **August 16, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Silhouette of Basketball Player  

Posted on: **July 12, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Simple Flat Geometric Shapes  

Posted on: **July 13, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Smoke and Sparks  

Posted on: **May 08, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Solar Panels on a Roof  

Posted on: **May 25, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Spaceship Corridor  

Posted on: **February 01, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Sunset  

Posted on: **January 18, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Supernova Nebula  

Posted on: **April 05, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Survivor  

Posted on: **October 12, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Technical Graph  

Posted on: **May 08, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Tesseract  

Posted on: **June 14, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Triangle Abstract  

Posted on: **June 15, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Ultra Modern House  

Posted on: **July 05, 2023**  
Generative AI

Select Report tagging error

###### Vacation  

Posted on: **June 07, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Vertical Panels Glowing  

Posted on: **July 20, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Vibrant Neon Light Behind Eclipse  

Posted on: **August 03, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Volcano Eruption  

Posted on: **March 08, 2023**  
Unconfirmed AI Image

Select Report tagging error

###### Watercolor Drawing  

Posted on: **August 10, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Watercolor Landscape  

Posted on: **August 10, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Wedding  

Posted on: **May 31, 2023**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Wet Asphalt With Neon Light  

Posted on: **November 30, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Window to Mountains  

Posted on: **December 14, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

###### Winter landscape  

Posted on: **October 05, 2022**  
Real (Not AI)

Select Report tagging error

Images are all licensed

##### What's New

**

What's New:  

**1) New form layout.  
2) Pre-field link support ([demo](https://myevent.cc/VBAr))  
3) Remove branding for ~$4~ $2  
more to come**

**

##### Report

report {{img\_NAME}}. image is listed as {{tag}} but it need the {{users report}}.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Close

You are not loged in.

### Basic info

By continuing you have agree with the [Privacy Policy](#)

* * *

 Countdown Name

 Countdown Date

 Time (24hr format)

none Africa/AbidjanAfrica/AccraAfrica/Addis\_AbabaAfrica/AlgiersAfrica/AsmaraAfrica/BamakoAfrica/BanguiAfrica/BanjulAfrica/BissauAfrica/BlantyreAfrica/BrazzavilleAfrica/BujumburaAfrica/CairoAfrica/CasablancaAfrica/CeutaAfrica/ConakryAfrica/DakarAfrica/Dar\_es\_SalaamAfrica/DjiboutiAfrica/DoualaAfrica/El\_AaiunAfrica/FreetownAfrica/GaboroneAfrica/HarareAfrica/JohannesburgAfrica/JubaAfrica/KampalaAfrica/KhartoumAfrica/KigaliAfrica/KinshasaAfrica/LagosAfrica/LibrevilleAfrica/LomeAfrica/LuandaAfrica/LubumbashiAfrica/LusakaAfrica/MalaboAfrica/MaputoAfrica/MaseruAfrica/MbabaneAfrica/MogadishuAfrica/MonroviaAfrica/NairobiAfrica/NdjamenaAfrica/NiameyAfrica/NouakchottAfrica/OuagadougouAfrica/Porto-NovoAfrica/Sao\_TomeAfrica/TripoliAfrica/TunisAfrica/WindhoekAmerica/AdakAmerica/AnchorageAmerica/AnguillaAmerica/AntiguaAmerica/AraguainaAmerica/Argentina/Buenos\_AiresAmerica/Argentina/CatamarcaAmerica/Argentina/CordobaAmerica/Argentina/JujuyAmerica/Argentina/La\_RiojaAmerica/Argentina/MendozaAmerica/Argentina/Rio\_GallegosAmerica/Argentina/SaltaAmerica/Argentina/San\_JuanAmerica/Argentina/San\_LuisAmerica/Argentina/TucumanAmerica/Argentina/UshuaiaAmerica/ArubaAmerica/AsuncionAmerica/AtikokanAmerica/BahiaAmerica/Bahia\_BanderasAmerica/BarbadosAmerica/BelemAmerica/BelizeAmerica/Blanc-SablonAmerica/Boa\_VistaAmerica/BogotaAmerica/BoiseAmerica/Cambridge\_BayAmerica/Campo\_GrandeAmerica/CancunAmerica/CaracasAmerica/CayenneAmerica/CaymanAmerica/ChicagoAmerica/ChihuahuaAmerica/Ciudad\_JuarezAmerica/Costa\_RicaAmerica/CrestonAmerica/CuiabaAmerica/CuracaoAmerica/DanmarkshavnAmerica/DawsonAmerica/Dawson\_CreekAmerica/DenverAmerica/DetroitAmerica/DominicaAmerica/EdmontonAmerica/EirunepeAmerica/El\_SalvadorAmerica/Fort\_NelsonAmerica/FortalezaAmerica/Glace\_BayAmerica/Goose\_BayAmerica/Grand\_TurkAmerica/GrenadaAmerica/GuadeloupeAmerica/GuatemalaAmerica/GuayaquilAmerica/GuyanaAmerica/HalifaxAmerica/HavanaAmerica/HermosilloAmerica/Indiana/IndianapolisAmerica/Indiana/KnoxAmerica/Indiana/MarengoAmerica/Indiana/PetersburgAmerica/Indiana/Tell\_CityAmerica/Indiana/VevayAmerica/Indiana/VincennesAmerica/Indiana/WinamacAmerica/InuvikAmerica/IqaluitAmerica/JamaicaAmerica/JuneauAmerica/Kentucky/LouisvilleAmerica/Kentucky/MonticelloAmerica/KralendijkAmerica/La\_PazAmerica/LimaAmerica/Los\_AngelesAmerica/Lower\_PrincesAmerica/MaceioAmerica/ManaguaAmerica/ManausAmerica/MarigotAmerica/MartiniqueAmerica/MatamorosAmerica/MazatlanAmerica/MenomineeAmerica/MeridaAmerica/MetlakatlaAmerica/Mexico\_CityAmerica/MiquelonAmerica/MonctonAmerica/MonterreyAmerica/MontevideoAmerica/MontserratAmerica/NassauAmerica/New\_YorkAmerica/NomeAmerica/NoronhaAmerica/North\_Dakota/BeulahAmerica/North\_Dakota/CenterAmerica/North\_Dakota/New\_SalemAmerica/NuukAmerica/OjinagaAmerica/PanamaAmerica/ParamariboAmerica/PhoenixAmerica/Port-au-PrinceAmerica/Port\_of\_SpainAmerica/Porto\_VelhoAmerica/Puerto\_RicoAmerica/Punta\_ArenasAmerica/Rankin\_InletAmerica/RecifeAmerica/ReginaAmerica/ResoluteAmerica/Rio\_BrancoAmerica/SantaremAmerica/SantiagoAmerica/Santo\_DomingoAmerica/Sao\_PauloAmerica/ScoresbysundAmerica/SitkaAmerica/St\_BarthelemyAmerica/St\_JohnsAmerica/St\_KittsAmerica/St\_LuciaAmerica/St\_ThomasAmerica/St\_VincentAmerica/Swift\_CurrentAmerica/TegucigalpaAmerica/ThuleAmerica/TijuanaAmerica/TorontoAmerica/TortolaAmerica/VancouverAmerica/WhitehorseAmerica/WinnipegAmerica/YakutatAntarctica/CaseyAntarctica/DavisAntarctica/DumontDUrvilleAntarctica/MacquarieAntarctica/MawsonAntarctica/McMurdoAntarctica/PalmerAntarctica/RotheraAntarctica/SyowaAntarctica/TrollAntarctica/VostokArctic/LongyearbyenAsia/AdenAsia/AlmatyAsia/AmmanAsia/AnadyrAsia/AqtauAsia/AqtobeAsia/AshgabatAsia/AtyrauAsia/BaghdadAsia/BahrainAsia/BakuAsia/BangkokAsia/BarnaulAsia/BeirutAsia/BishkekAsia/BruneiAsia/ChitaAsia/ChoibalsanAsia/ColomboAsia/DamascusAsia/DhakaAsia/DiliAsia/DubaiAsia/DushanbeAsia/FamagustaAsia/GazaAsia/HebronAsia/Ho\_Chi\_MinhAsia/Hong\_KongAsia/HovdAsia/IrkutskAsia/JakartaAsia/JayapuraAsia/JerusalemAsia/KabulAsia/KamchatkaAsia/KarachiAsia/KathmanduAsia/KhandygaAsia/KolkataAsia/KrasnoyarskAsia/Kuala\_LumpurAsia/KuchingAsia/KuwaitAsia/MacauAsia/MagadanAsia/MakassarAsia/ManilaAsia/MuscatAsia/NicosiaAsia/NovokuznetskAsia/NovosibirskAsia/OmskAsia/OralAsia/Phnom\_PenhAsia/PontianakAsia/PyongyangAsia/QatarAsia/QostanayAsia/QyzylordaAsia/RiyadhAsia/SakhalinAsia/SamarkandAsia/SeoulAsia/ShanghaiAsia/SingaporeAsia/SrednekolymskAsia/TaipeiAsia/TashkentAsia/TbilisiAsia/TehranAsia/ThimphuAsia/TokyoAsia/TomskAsia/UlaanbaatarAsia/UrumqiAsia/Ust-NeraAsia/VientianeAsia/VladivostokAsia/YakutskAsia/YangonAsia/YekaterinburgAsia/YerevanAtlantic/AzoresAtlantic/BermudaAtlantic/CanaryAtlantic/Cape\_VerdeAtlantic/FaroeAtlantic/MadeiraAtlantic/ReykjavikAtlantic/South\_GeorgiaAtlantic/St\_HelenaAtlantic/StanleyAustralia/AdelaideAustralia/BrisbaneAustralia/Broken\_HillAustralia/DarwinAustralia/EuclaAustralia/HobartAustralia/LindemanAustralia/Lord\_HoweAustralia/MelbourneAustralia/PerthAustralia/SydneyEurope/AmsterdamEurope/AndorraEurope/AstrakhanEurope/AthensEurope/BelgradeEurope/BerlinEurope/BratislavaEurope/BrusselsEurope/BucharestEurope/BudapestEurope/BusingenEurope/ChisinauEurope/CopenhagenEurope/DublinEurope/GibraltarEurope/GuernseyEurope/HelsinkiEurope/Isle\_of\_ManEurope/IstanbulEurope/JerseyEurope/KaliningradEurope/KirovEurope/KyivEurope/LisbonEurope/LjubljanaEurope/LondonEurope/LuxembourgEurope/MadridEurope/MaltaEurope/MariehamnEurope/MinskEurope/MonacoEurope/MoscowEurope/OsloEurope/ParisEurope/PodgoricaEurope/PragueEurope/RigaEurope/RomeEurope/SamaraEurope/San\_MarinoEurope/SarajevoEurope/SaratovEurope/SimferopolEurope/SkopjeEurope/SofiaEurope/StockholmEurope/TallinnEurope/TiraneEurope/UlyanovskEurope/VaduzEurope/VaticanEurope/ViennaEurope/VilniusEurope/VolgogradEurope/WarsawEurope/ZagrebEurope/ZurichIndian/AntananarivoIndian/ChagosIndian/ChristmasIndian/CocosIndian/ComoroIndian/KerguelenIndian/MaheIndian/MaldivesIndian/MauritiusIndian/MayotteIndian/ReunionPacific/ApiaPacific/AucklandPacific/BougainvillePacific/ChathamPacific/ChuukPacific/EasterPacific/EfatePacific/FakaofoPacific/FijiPacific/FunafutiPacific/GalapagosPacific/GambierPacific/GuadalcanalPacific/GuamPacific/HonoluluPacific/KantonPacific/KiritimatiPacific/KosraePacific/KwajaleinPacific/MajuroPacific/MarquesasPacific/MidwayPacific/NauruPacific/NiuePacific/NorfolkPacific/NoumeaPacific/Pago\_PagoPacific/PalauPacific/PitcairnPacific/PohnpeiPacific/Port\_MoresbyPacific/RarotongaPacific/SaipanPacific/TahitiPacific/TarawaPacific/TongatapuPacific/WakePacific/Wallis Timezone  

Note: Please be advised that the information entered will be displayed on the countdown page and may be utilized by the APIs and/or services used by customcountdown.io. To ensure privacy, please refrain from entering any personally identifiable information.

##### Testing, Do Not Use

 Select Date and Time

### What message would you like to be displayed after **{{C\_name}}** ends?

 Completed Message

Tip: You can now link a YouTube video to your page and use it as the message. This feature only works with YouTube videos. Any other type of content will be displayed as-is.

### Would you like to include a description for **{{C\_name}}**?

Description (Optional)

### Choose an image to use as the background for **{{C\_name}}**.

Select Background Image

Selected: Default

_Upgrade for unlimited ad-free pages and custom backgrounds. $60/yr at Jordan3590.com_

### Other

Accent Color    

Days, Hours, Minutes, Seconds Days, Hours, Minutes Months, Days, Hours, Minutes, Seconds Months, Days, Hours, Minutes Clock Format  
eventclock.co c.jo51.co myevent.cc (Deprecat on June 1, 2025) Short URL Domain  

 Remove branding for a one-time fee of $2.

_[Unlimited Ad-Free Pages for $60/yr with Jordan3590.com](https://jordan3590.com/)_

Captcha not working?  
**Make Countdown** _By submitting this form, you hereby consent to **JORDAN3590** storing all the information associated with this form. This information includes, but is not limited to: your countdown name, date, and the corresponding short URL. Please note that all information will be retained for 5 days after the expiration date of the countdown. After this period, the information will be permanently removed from the database. The names and URLs of all created countdown will be included in a system-generated email that will be sent to **JORDAN3590**. Your IP (51.195.149.220) will be used to find out what country you are in. Your country name will be put in your page's 'more info' section._

Back

Next

### Sample Text

Sample Text
-----------
